[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
You scared me!
Look, if you're sleepy,
just go upstairs to get some proper sleep.
I wasn't sleeping. I was meditating.
Meditating?
Where's Ming Yu?
Hasn't he been back for days?
He hasn't been home
since he got back from Ma'ao.
Don't act like you didn't know.
Come on.
Isn't this all part of your little scheme
with Zheng?
Scheme? What scheme?
Keep acting.
You...
You and him
had Ming Yu take his daughter to Ma'ao
just to push them together, didn't you?
You think I can't see right through that?
Zheng had the idea.
I couldn't exactly say no, could I?
The point is,
we've watched You An grow up.
We know her background well.
That's exactly why
I don't want anything to do with them.
Look, let the young people
figure it out themselves.
Who knows. Maybe they'll hit it off in Ma'ao.
I don't want to hear it.
You two have some nerve.
Ming Yu went there for work.
It's a business trip.
Yet you added a burden to his plate.
Honestly, you've gone too far.
Well,
you're against this only because
you don't like You An's mother.
Stepmother.
So what if she's the in-law?
We can keep our distance after that, can't we?
In-law?
Surprise!
So handsome!
Ming Yu.
Is she tired?
Hurry up.
Smile! Say cheese!
You're 100 days old!
How lovely!
Oh, my!
What did I do in a past life
to deserve Dong Xian as my in-law?
If heaven could send some destined girl
to capture Ming Yu's heart,
I'd go vegetarian for a year!
[Episode 12]
[A Complete Love Rat]
She's not home, indeed.
Good.
How can we set up the surprise if she's here?
- Let's go.
- Go.
Is it ready? I'm hungry.
Okay. Done.
Time to eat.
Nice cooking.
You even carved the carrot?
But you made so much.
I might not finish it all.
You will finish it.
Or I'll reduce your year-end bonus.
What are you wiping?
Lipstick.
Don't want it ending up in the food.
No need. It looks good.
What's gotten into you today?
Took a crash course in emotional quotient?
Eat up.
Thanks.
And there's a cake, too?
Mr. Fu, you're quite prepared.
"Dear 'Captain' Ruan,"
"if the road ahead is long,
may it be lined with flowers and light."
"And if it's not, don't be afraid,
because we're right here with you."
"Be a proud princess."
"Love you forever."
Actually,
I ordered it on behalf of Hengshi Air.
On this card are the best wishes
and appreciation
from all the employees.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Good job!
- You're really something.
- Of course.
Looks like "Captain" Ruan
doesn't want her bonus reduced.
Who does?
[Dong Xian]
Hello?
I'm good. I've already eaten.
How do you know where I live?
It's raining out there.
You should head back.
Okay.
I'll be there soon.
Boss, do you have an umbrella?
Yes.
- What do you need it for?
- I need to get something downstairs.
It's pouring out there.
I'll go.
Thanks.
Auntie Dong, sorry to keep you waiting.
Ming Yu.
Where's Ruan?
It's too rainy, so I didn't have her come down.
Mr. Fu, may I ask you,
what's your relationship with Ruan right now?
At work, she's my employee.
After hours, I'd say we're friends.
Just friends?
Auntie Dong,
what we become depends on how Si Xian sees it.
I can ask her when I go upstairs later.
Alright. I'll leave it to you then.
I'll make sure she gets your wishes.
The rain's really heavy.
Be careful on your way back.
Thanks, Ming Yu.
You're back?
Auntie Dong asked me a few days ago
if you were scheduled to work today.
- Did you tell her?
- No.
I have professional ethics, you know?
It's the same as the one you ordered.
"Don't mention... Dad."
She's my mom.
She just asked me what we are.
And what did you say?
I told her we're friends.
Yes, that's right.
We're friends.
Since we're friends, come with me.
I have a birthday gift for you.
- You'll take it, won't you?
- What is it?
Right this way.
So many plane models!
Do you like them?
I thought you were giving me a real one.
That's not out of the question.
But there'd be conditions.
Are these all your collection?
Yes.
You're really giving me one?
- Take your pick.
- Then I won't hold back.
I'll take...
Z101.
I never said you could only pick one.
Really?
You can take whatever you like in this room.
What if I like everything?
Does that include me?
Fu Ming Yu!
Are you trying to take advantage of me?
You were going to hit me again.
And kick me too.
Today,
you look really beautiful.
Well... I'll be going now.
Surprise! Happy birthday!
You scared me to death!
Your cake.
I don't want it. Keep it for yourself.
I'll leave it by the door.
Remember to take it in.
Spill.
We've been waiting for ages.
Where were you?
What were you doing with Fu Ming Yu?
Tell us everything.
I...
Speak up.
What did you eat for dinner?
- Longevity noodles.
- Only noodles?
A vice president like him ordered you noodles?
It wasn't takeout.
He cooked them for me.
What?
A vice president like him cooked for you?
Alright, can we stop talking about food?
Fine, you ask.
Good.
What exactly did you two do tonight?
He cooked, I ate, I picked a gift,
and then I came back.
- That's it?
- That's all.
- Then why were you so flustered?
- Were I?
You were.
When you came in and shut the door,
you were breathing hard.
And your face was red.
I swear, that's because I ran down the stairs.
I didn't take the elevator.
Could one floor make a woman
as strong as you pant?
And he even got you a cake.
One was from my mom, the other was from him
on behalf of the company.
I've been at Hengshi Air for seven years,
and never gotten that kind of treatment.
Poor thing.
Open it and see.
It's smashed.
It went through some stuff.
Still edible, though.
Didn't you have any?
Didn't get to. I came straight back.
Why did you come back so early?
Was he trying something?
No.
I had to get the plane model back
before he changed his mind.
Sure.
"If the road ahead is long..."
Aren't those my lines?
They really are.
She's got a good poker face.
We've been grilling her all night
and got nothing.
I don't think you need to ask anymore.
Something's definitely going on.
But one thing's for sure.
Your job is safe, right?
Park yourself.
I can't even tell whose car this is.
I'm the one driving it every day.
Drive safe.
Today is Ruan's birthday.
Xuan and I found out
she's got something going on
with our vice president.
Grilled her all night and she wouldn't crack.
She's got a steel trap of a mouth.
You've got a pretty tight mouth too.
Still haven't confessed.
How much longer are you going to sleep here?
It must be the period, the hormones.
That's the only reason I'd be thinking of him.
Stop thinking about him.
Period mode: lock up my heart.
No way.
The hormones are really hitting hard.
Have you had breakfast?
Yes.
It's raining out there.
Might be hard to get a taxi.
Get changed. I'll wait for you downstairs.
Mr. Fu.
Today's flight might not
be able to take off as scheduled.
Should I notify them in advance?
Got it.
I'm going to the U.S. today.
I'll be back in 10 days.
So?
Just letting you know.
What's there to tell me?
You can hop out here. I'll go park.
But it's raining outside.
I'll have to walk in the rain.
If I go to the parking lot,
you'll have to walk even further, right?
Isn't this closer?
Can't you drop me off at the entrance?
- Which entrance?
- The main entrance.
Usually only the president parks there, right?
If I park there now
and another colleague sees us, what then?
It's raining. I'm not getting out here.
You're really harsh with your words.
A taxi would pull up to that entrance too.
Am I a taxi driver?
If I pull up there, they'll recognize my car.
You're afraid of being seen.
I wasn't even thinking about that.
That's exactly what you meant.
If people see us and ask,
I'll say I ran into you in the rain,
and you kindly gave me a ride.
And honestly, who's going to ask me that?
Are you new to the workplace?
People gossip. They'll definitely ask.
Then I'll have to waste time explaining--
You don't want to explain,
so I have to walk in the rain?
Take an umbrella.
Yue Yang,
if I were just any random colleague,
I wouldn't even get treated like this.
Look, there's no "any random colleague."
This seat has only ever been yours.
No other woman has sat here,
not even any of the guys.
- Really?
- Really.
When you're not here,
I keep a photo of you right there,
and a pile of snacks next to it.
It's my way of telling people
this seat's taken.
Her name is Jiang Zi Yue, right?
Then swear on it.
You swear.
I know what you're thinking.
You want people to know
how good we are together.
But I think we can
keep that happiness between us, right?
Why do we need the fanfare and
let other people watch and prove something?
Besides, you're gorgeous and talented.
Your colleagues are nowhere near your level.
If they get jealous, I can't even imagine
what that'd look like.
You and your sweet talk.
That's all you've got.
That's not all I've got.
You only do things like this when I'm mad.
Alright, don't be mad.
You'll be late.
Go on.
I'm going.
Go ahead.
Thanks.
What are you gawking at?
Good morning, mentor.
I just saw Ruan Si Xian
get out of Mr. Fu's car.
- Really?
- For real.
Mr. Fu's car is right there.
He dropped her off himself.
Mentor, I was literally giving her advice
the other day on how to go after him.
What a joke.
The clown was me all along.
What time is your flight?
Aren't you worried about being late?
I'm running late!
I've got to go. See you later.
[Lu Ming]
Xiao Zhen.
Please listen to me...
Lu Ming?
[Jiang City]
Yes, this one.
Ni Tong, we're leaving.
- Bye.
- Stay safe.
When will this rain let up?
With this many people waiting,
I'll be stuck here forever.
Ni Tong.
- Ruan.
- Get a taxi yet?
Not yet.
Still twenty-something cars ahead.
Where are you going?
A friend's picking me up.
We can give you a ride.
Ruan, does this friend happen to be Mr. Fu?
Then you can wait for your own ride.
What, I can't even ask?
Xiao Zhen, where are you?
I'm at the parking lot now.
I've landed.
How's the weather over there?
[Recall]
I must have been crazy.
Why did I text him?
The number you have dialed is powered off.
Sorry...
Why's it off?
Hello, Ruan.
Hello, Xuan.
I've landed, but I can't reach Xiao Zhen.
When did she leave the pub?
She left the pub quite a while ago.
Said she was going to see Lu Ming,
and then head to the airport to pick you up.
Hasn't she shown up yet?
No. Her phone's off.
What if something's happened?
I've been waiting forever.
Listen, don't panic.
We've got Lu Ming's address in the group chat.
- I'll head over right now.
- Okay, I'm coming too.
Let's meet there.
Ruan? What are you doing?
Ruan, this is my ride.
Where's your friend?
My friend might be in trouble.
I'll pay for everything.
Go. Get in.
- Hurry up.
- Wait...
We're going to Ruifeng Garden.
Come on, Ruan! I waited so long for this ride.
Quiet.
I can't reach Xiao Zhen.
Please, step on it.
Xiao Zhen!
It's so late, why are you sitting here?
- Where's Lu Ming?
- I've been waiting and waiting.
I don't know where he went.
He's not here.
Don't cry. Crying won't help.
- Xiao Zhen, where's Lu Ming?
- It's okay.
Ruan.
- There, there. It's okay. Don't cry.
- I can't find Lu Ming...
Here. Drink this while it's hot.
- I have one, too?
- You got caught in the rain too.
Thanks.
Ruan, don't waste it on her.
She left you stranded at the airport for a guy.
I never took her for that type,
ditching her friend for a man.
I'm not that type!
You're not that type?
You're worse.
- How could you leave Ruan--
- Xuan.
Ruan.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to
leave you at the airport.
I didn't know what to do.
I wanted to ask him face to face.
Why does he ignore me every time he goes out,
doesn't reply to texts, doesn't pick up calls?
Why hasn't he contacted me in so long?
And my phone died. I got carried away.
I didn't mean to put you second.
Okay, I know you're not that kind of person.
Si Xiao Zhen, is it worth it for a jerk?
"Going out," "business trips"...
These are the warm-ups before he ghosts you.
Once they're out, they're wild.
And they can conveniently tell you
they're "too busy."
He doesn't care one bit about how you feel.
He's not like that.
- He always told me--
- Sweet talk's called sweet for a reason.
Tong Le, come over here.
Give us a few lines of your best sweet talk.
Before I met you,
I didn't really have a plan for my life.
But now I do.
I've selfishly included you in my future.
I'm not the gentle type, but for you, I can be.
I didn't even know how to make drinks,
but I learned it, just so I could stay here.
So whether you think it's love at first sight
or just pure obsession,
I don't care.
I just want you to know, for you,
I'd change everything about myself--
- Alright, that's enough.
- I...
See? Men will say anything to charm a woman.
- I meant every word.
- Are you done?
Finished the glasses? Go work.
Got it.
Men will say anything to get what they want.
One minute they're all over you,
the next they give you the cold shoulder
without a second thought.
You ask them
why they don't remember the good times.
What good times?
You made all that up in your head.
Fine.
For argument's sake,
are you even officially together?
Has he ever confessed to you?
Silence is how adults say goodbye.
And you were dumb enough
to go knock on his door
and make yourself look this pathetic.
Today,
you look really beautiful.
I'm going to the U.S. today.
I'll be back in 10 days.
Scumbag.
A complete love rat.
Back then, didn't Ruan and I both tell you
this guy was unreliable?
Didn't we both tell you to take it slow?
You didn't listen to a word.
The tears you're shedding now
are the water you let into your head back then.
Let them out.
Maybe I made him invest too much time
without giving him anything back?
Maybe he just ran out of patience?
Now you're still blaming yourself?
Ghosting is a classic move.
He's already moved on to the next one,
and you're still trying to figure out
what you did wrong?
Alright, Xiao Zhen.
Whatever the reason, you have to face reality.
Sudden disappearances like this
usually mean one of three things.
First, he found someone else.
Second, his real girlfriend found out.
Third, most likely, he's in jail.
Which one is it, then?
Doesn't matter which one.
You need to act
like this guy never even existed.
Alright, stop being sad.
Finish this drink, forget the jerk.
Goodbye to him, on to the next.
You're so good to me.
Still cold?
Not anymore.
[United States]
So, what's the deal with Charles?
Leaving us hanging like this. Pretty rude.
He's late.
We're not here on behalf of the company,
and he knows why I came.
He's putting on airs.
If I'd known,
we wouldn't have to come this early.
You haven't eaten a thing.
We could've grabbed something
instead of just sitting here waiting.
Let's wait a bit.
If we didn't come early,
we might not catch him at all.
When he shows up, your jet lag kicks in.
Can you hold up?
I was thinking I could take you to Chinatown.
There's an amazing hotpot place.
Little stools, little tables, spicy hotpot...
- Even local Chinese go there. Really good--
- I don't eat spicy food.
How did they both get this drunk?
Tong Le, what did you put in that ginger tea?
Red wine.
Red wine? Which bottle?
The one under your cabinet.
Saw you hadn't finished it till today.
Didn't want it to go to waste.
No.
My Romanée-Conti.
And now it tastes like ginger.
What a waste.
Go!
Easy!
- Where's the light?
- Light...
There, on your left.
Close the door!
The suitcase! Almost forgot it.
Wait, change your shoes!
Seriously?
I can barely hold her up.
I'll get her on the bed.
Easy.
My goodness.
- Easy.
- Give me a hand.
Careful.
There we go. Wait outside.
I'll change her clothes.
Alright, I'll grab some water.
Tong Le, from now on, whenever they come,
you're not to give them a drop of alcohol
unless they're accompanied.
Did you...
What did you say?
I said, drinking's better with company.
Who do you want to have with you?
How about me?
Is there no internet over there?
Can't send me a message?
[Fu Ming Yu]
Thank you very much. Nice to meet you guys.
- Likewise.
- Have a nice trip. See you.
- See you.
- See you. Bye, guys.
See you.
This afternoon, right? Okay.
Hello?
Is this Fu Ming Yu?
- It's me.
- So your phone didn't get lost.
And it's not broken either.
Every time you go on a business trip,
you pretend to be busy,
and you don't send a single message.
You're but a player.
Get a little taste, and you're gone.
- Have you been drinking?
- No.
I'm perfectly clear-headed.
I'm about to make a major decision.
I'm kicking you out.
Kick you out of my head.
I'm done thinking about you.
You jerk.
You think buying me a birthday cake
gives you some kind of status?
Not even close.
I'm locking my heart up.
I'm going to be immune.
I'm listening to Xuan,
no more believing men's sweet talk.
No more believing you.
Scumbag.
Mr. Fu.
We need to cut this trip short.
I need to get back earlier.
Are we skipping hotpot?